

CONTACT ME

070-9034-4134

sunnyliumifune@gmail.com

https://github.com/SunnyMifune

in www.linkedin.com/in/sunnymifune

EDUCATION

Web Development

Le Wagon Tokyo

2022.10-2022.12

Business Administration Dept. Soochow University/Master degree 2017-2018

Business Administration Dept. Soochow University/Bachelor degree2013-2017

SKILLS

HTML JavaScript ES6

CSS SQL

Bootstrap Ruby on Rails

LANGUAGES

Mandarin: native

English: fluent

Japanese: conversational

Sunny Mifune

Junior frontend engineer

ABOUT ME

I was born and grew up in Taiwan. I love classical music and began violin study since 6 years old. Also, I have joined the Taipei civic symphony orchestra for 9 years!

I'm self-motivated, mature, and have a strong sense of responsibility with a positive working attitude.

I have an MBA degree from Soochow University and now come to Tokyo to learn web development and want to have experience in developer position.

WEB DEVELOPMENT PROJECTS

Freshout (Team role: front-end + back-end)

http://www.freshout.world/

The app can easily show what food the user has in their fridge, and the app also can inform users of the expiration date to prevent the waste of food.

// Ruby on Rails, HTML, CSS, Javascript, API

Farm-bnb (Team role: front-end)

https://farm-bnb.herokuapp.com/

Users can book the animals on the website when they need help from animals working for their farm.

// Ruby on Rails, HTML, CSS, Javascript, API

WORK EXPERIENCE

Merchandiser (Pre-order Dept.)

2021.09-2022.09

Li & Fung Limited I Taipei, Taiwan

- Communicate and follow up with internal and external constituents, including clients, vendors, mills, and colleagues, to solve problems as soon as possible.
- Build and maintain close relationships with buyers in order to understand their goals and provide them with suitable sourcing services.

Logistic Assistant

2021.04-2021.09

KindMinds Innovations I Taipei, Taiwan

- Create sea or express shipment to send products oversea.
- Tracking packages if arrive on time and calculating the accounts receivable.
- Weekly checking the Amazon FBA system, sometime the system will have an error.

Assistant Merchandiser (Production Dept.)

2018.10-2020-06

Li & Fung Limited I Taipei, Taiwan

- Manage production for the children's accessories / active apparel industry, like monitoring the transit calendars, orders, production progress, and shipping to ensure deliveries.
- System information update.